Your life is your life.
Don't let it be gloved into dank submission.
Beyond the watch.
There are ways out.
There is a light somewhere.
It may not be much light, but it beats the darkness.
Beyond the watch, the gods will offer you chances.
Know them, take them.
You can't beat death, but you can beat death in life sometimes.
And the more often you learn to do it, the more light there will be.
Your life is your life.
Know it while you have it.
You are marvelous.
The gods wait to delight in you.
If you are going to try, go all the way.
Otherwise, don't even start.
This could mean losing girlfriends.
Fires, relatives, jobs, and maybe you'll mind.
Go all the way.
It could mean not eating for three or four days.
It could mean freezing on a path bench.
It could mean jail.
It could mean origin, mockery, isolation.
Isolation is the gift.
All the others are a test of your endurance.
Of how much you really want to do it.
And you do it.
Despite rejection and the worst odds, and it will be better than anything else you can
imagine.
If you are going to try, go all the way.
There is no other feeling like that.
You will be alone with the gods and the nights will play in the fire.
Do it.
All the way.
You will ride mine straight to perfect laughter.
Until you understand what life here is.